Mert Kaan İrtegün

Frontend Developer

Profile

Front-end developer with proven experience in Armut(Homerun in Europe), Poplar and Insider, helping companies develop new features and improve existing code contents. Knows modern javascript frameworks and libraries, is open to learning and closely follows new developments in the software world.

Professional Experience

Professional Experience			
 Frontend Developer, PhiTech ☑ Responsible for develoing new fut newly created projects Angular, Javascript 	tures, development	of the architechture of	12/2023 – present Kocaeli, Turkey
 Frontend Developer, Armut Homerun ☑ Responsible for developing new features, improving existing code quality React, React Native, Angular, javascript, Jenkins, Jest, Cypress 			02/2022 – 12/2023 Istanbul, Turkey
 Frontend Developer, Carvak ☑ Responsible for the establishment created projects improving the SE Vue 2, Nuxt, Vuex, Vuetify, HTML/T 	O scores of the rela	nted projects	07/2021 – 01/2022 Istanbul, Turkey
Frontend Developer, Insider ☑ • Javascript, Jquery, Vue, Vuex			02/2021 – 07/2021 Istanbul, Turkey
Skills			
React Redux, React Native, React Hooks	• • • •	Angular RxJs, Angular11+, NgRx	• • • •
Vue Vuex, Nuxt	• • • •	Javascript Node.js, Jquery, Es6, Es7, V	• • • • • ⁄anilla.js
Typescript	• • • •	C/C++	• • • • •
Education			

Languages

English	French	German
C1	A1	A2

09/2016 – 07/2021 Istanbul, Turkey

Projects

Personal Portfolio

Bachelor's Degree, Istanbul Technical University ☑

It is my portfolio site that contains my personal information and a few of my projects.